<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>St Vrain Archery Club</title>
    <link>https://paulprogrammer.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on St Vrain Archery Club</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 12:46:56 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://paulprogrammer.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>New Saint Vrain Archery and Bowhunter&#39;s Club website</title>
      <link>https://paulprogrammer.github.io/news-events/new-saint-vrain-archery-and-bowhunter-s-club-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2019 12:46:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulprogrammer.github.io/news-events/new-saint-vrain-archery-and-bowhunter-s-club-website/</guid>
      <description>This is the new Saint Vrain Archery and Bowhunters Club website. told old site is outdated and we can no longer maintain it.
The URL is svarchery.net. Please save this in your browser.
Updates will be posted only here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Range Damage</title>
      <link>https://paulprogrammer.github.io/news-events/article01/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2017 20:15:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulprogrammer.github.io/news-events/article01/</guid>
      <description>A range survey will be done in March to assess damage that occurred over the winter.
The range is operable where shooting positions are still intact. For those who may be out shooting, please pick up any target pieces you find and place them near the target to which they belong. If you can make minor repairs feel free to do so.
Each year there are at least two and usually three Saturday work days planned after the eagle hour restrictions are lifted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eagle Restrictions are now in Effect</title>
      <link>https://paulprogrammer.github.io/news-events/article02/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://paulprogrammer.github.io/news-events/article02/</guid>
      <description>Restricted range hours went into effect on November 15th, 2018. You should not be at the range or anywhere on the property except from 9:00 am to 3:00 pm.
The club supports the Colorado Parks and Wildlife restrictions for the range because it is a bald eagle roosting and nesting area.
There are no member exceptions to this restriction for any reason. Presence at the range outside these hours technically is consider trespassing.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>